https://www.northropgrumman.com/who-we-are/privacy-policy/

This website is best viewed in browsers such as: Edge, Firefox, Chrome, or Safari. We encourage you to use one of these browsers for the best experience.
Skip to content
Who We Are
Company Leadership
Global Presence
Corporate Responsibility
Investors
Suppliers
News
Effective September 28, 2020
We at Northrop Grumman respect your concerns about privacy. This Online Privacy Notice applies to northropgrumman.com and other external Northrop Grumman websites that link to this Notice (the “Sites”). This Notice describes the types of personal information we collect on the Sites, how we use the information, with whom we share it and the choices available to users of our Sites regarding our use of the information. We also describe the measures we take to protect the security of the information and how users can contact us about our privacy practices. Certain of the Sites may provide additional detail about privacy practices specific to those Sites. Internal company policies and procedures govern Northrop Grumman's internal networks and systems and the processing of personal information relating to employees and other authorized Northrop Grumman network users.
For California residents, please click here for additional information on how we process your personal information.
Click on one of the links below to jump to the listed section:
Information We Collect
How We Use the Information We Collect
Interest-Based Advertising
Information We Share
Your Rights and Choices
Data Transfers
How We Protect Personal Information
Links To Other Websites
Updates To Our Online Privacy Notice
How To Contact Us
Information We Collect
The types of personal information users of our Sites may submit include:
contact information (such as name, postal address, telephone number and email address);
employment information (such as title, division and employer), including military rank;
login credentials for the Sites;
other personal information submitted by current or prospective suppliers and subcontractors, such as Social Security number, diversity-related information (such as ethnicity), federal tax ID number, disability status, and civil and criminal court history;
other personal information submitted by job applicants, such as a résumé or C.V., work authorization information, salary history, education history, information about security clearances, citizenship information and, for jobs with U.S.-based Northrop Grumman entities, ethnicity, race and gender; and
other personal information found in content that users provide.
Information We Collect By Automated Means
When you use our Sites, we may collect certain information by automated means, using technologies such as cookies, web server logs, web beacons and JavaScript.
Cookies are files that websites send to your computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify your browser or to store information or settings on your device. Our Sites may use cookies (such as HTTP and HTML5 cookies) and Flash cookies, as well as other types of local storage (such as browser-based or plugin-based local storage). Your browser may tell you how to be notified when you receive certain types of cookies and how to restrict or disable certain cookies. You also may be able to delete your Flash cookies or adjust your Flash cookie settings by visiting the Adobe Flash Website Storage Settings Panel and Global Storage Settings Panel. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to use all of the features of our Sites or other websites and online services.
In conjunction with gathering information through cookies, our web servers may log information such as your device type, operating system type, browser type, domain, and other system settings, as well as the language your system uses and the country and time zone where your device is located. We also may record information such as the address of the web page that referred you to our Sites and the IP address of the device you use to connect to our Sites. We also may log information about your interaction with the Sites, such as which pages you visit. We may place tags on our web pages called “web beacons,” which are small files that link web pages to particular web servers and their cookies.
We may use third-party web analytics services on our Sites, such as those of Google Analytics, Adobe Omniture, ScorecardResearch and DocAve Analytics. These service providers help us analyze how users use the Sites. The information collected for this purpose (including your IP address and other information collected by automated means) will be disclosed to or collected directly by these service providers. To learn more about how to opt out of these third-party web analytic service providers' activities, click the relevant link below:
Google Analytics
Adobe Omniture
ScorecardResearch
DocAve Analytics
Both we and others (such as our service providers and advertising networks) may collect personal information about our visitors' online activities, over time and across third-party websites. Our Sites are not designed to respond to “do not track” signals from browsers.
The providers of other third-party plug-ins on our Sites, such as embedded videos and social sharing tools, may use automated means to collect information regarding your use of the Sites and your interactions with the plug-ins. This information is subject to the privacy policies or notices of the third-party plug-in providers and is not subject to Northrop Grumman's Online Privacy Notice.
How We Use the Information We Collect
We may use the information described above to:
provide products and services;
send you promotional materials or other communications;
communicate with you about, and administer your participation in, special events, programs, offers, surveys and market research;
respond to your inquiries;
process employment applications, including by assessing qualifications, verifying information, and conducting reference or other employment-related checks;
evaluate potential suppliers and subcontractors and manage our relationships with them;
provide and administer human resources services for Northrop Grumman employees;
perform data analyses (including anonymization and aggregation of personal information);
operate, evaluate and improve our business (including developing new products and services; enhancing and improving our products and services; managing our communications; analyzing our products, services and communications; and performing accounting, auditing and other internal functions);
protect against, identify and prevent cybersecurity and other security events, espionage, fraud and other unlawful activity, claims and other liabilities; and
comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, relevant industry standards and our policies.
We also may use the information in other ways for which we provide specific notice at the time of collection.
In addition, we use information collected through automated means for the purposes set forth above, including by (i) customizing our users' visits to our Sites, (ii) analyzing the manner in which our users interact with our Sites and online advertisements, (iii) delivering content tailored to our users' interests and (iv) managing our Sites and other aspects of our business.
Interest-Based Advertising
On our Sites, we may collect information about your online activities for use in providing you with advertising about products and services tailored to your individual interests. This section of our Online Privacy Notice provides details and explains how to exercise your choices.
You may see certain ads on other websites because we participate in advertising networks. Ad networks allow us to target our messaging to users through demographic, interest-based and contextual means. These networks track your online activities over time by collecting information through automated means, including through the use of cookies, web server logs and web beacons. The networks use this information to show you advertisements that may be tailored to your individual interests. The information our ad networks may collect includes data about your visits to websites that participate in the relevant advertising networks, such as the pages or advertisements you view and the actions you take on the websites. This data collection takes place both on our Sites and on third-party websites that participate in the ad networks. This process also helps us track the effectiveness of our marketing efforts. To learn how to opt out of this ad network interest-based advertising, click here.
Information We Share
We do not sell or otherwise disclose personal information we collect about you, except as described in this Online Privacy Notice. We may share personal information with service providers who perform services on our behalf based on our instructions. We may share certain personal information with our affiliates for the purposes described in this Online Privacy Notice.
In addition, we may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law or legal process, (ii) to law enforcement authorities or other government entities, and (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent harm or financial loss, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual espionage, cybersecurity or security events or other fraudulent or illegal activity. We also reserve the right to transfer personal information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including in the event of a reorganization, spin-off, dissolution or liquidation).
Your Rights and Choices
We offer you certain choices in connection with the personal information we collect from you. To update your preferences, ask us to remove your information from our mailing lists or submit a request, please contact us as indicated in the “How To Contact Us” section of this Online Privacy Notice. To the extent provided by the law of your jurisdiction, you may request access to the personal information we maintain about you or request that we correct, amend, delete or block the information by contacting us as indicated below. Where provided by law, you may withdraw any consent you previously provided to us or object at any time on legitimate grounds to the processing of your personal information, and we will apply your preferences going forward.
To exercise your rights as a data subject or consumer:
For EU data subjects exercising rights in EU: GDPR – Data Subject Request Webform
For EU data subjects exercising rights in US: Privacy Shield – Data Subject Request Webform
For CA consumers exercising rights in CA: CCPA – Consumer Request Webform
Data Transfers
We may transfer the personal information we collect about you to recipients in countries other than the country in which the information originally was collected, including the U.S. Those countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer your information to recipients in other countries (such as the U.S.), we will protect that information as described in this Online Privacy Notice.
If you are located in the European Economic Area (“EEA”), the United Kingdom (“UK”) or Switzerland, we will comply with applicable legal requirements providing adequate protection for the transfer of personal information to recipients in countries outside of the EEA, the UK or Switzerland. The steps we take include entering into the European Commission’s Standard Contractual Clauses with the relevant data recipient, or ensuring that the data recipient has implemented Binding Corporate Rules. To obtain a copy of the safeguards we have put in place, please contact us as indicated below.
Northrop Grumman and its U.S. subsidiaries have certified that they comply with the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks and Privacy Shield Principles as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Commission regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information transferred from the EU, the UK or Switzerland to the U.S.. Click here to view our EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Privacy Notices and our participating U.S. subsidiaries. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/list. We no longer rely on the EU-U.S. or Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield to transfer personal information to the U.S.
How We Protect Personal Information
We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal information you provide on the Sites against accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use.
Links To Other Websites
Our Sites may provide links to other websites for your convenience and information. These websites may operate independently from us. Linked sites may have their own privacy notices or policies, which we strongly suggest you review. To the extent any linked websites are not owned or controlled by us, we are not responsible for the websites' content, any use of the websites, or the privacy practices of the websites, even though you may enter that site directly from visiting ours.
Updates To Our Online Privacy Notice
This Online Privacy Notice may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our personal information practices. We will post the updated version on our Sites and indicate at the top of the notice when it was most recently updated.
How To Contact Us
If you have any questions or comments about this Online Privacy Notice, or if you would like us to update information we have about you or your preferences, please contact us by filling out this information request form or writing to us at:
Northrop Grumman Systems Corporation
Attn: Corporate Communications/Privacy
2980 Fairview Park Drive
Falls Church, VA 22042
